Primary Menu

Privacy Policy
==============

MWQHJ LLC respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy governs your access to and use of mywifequitherjob.com, including any content, functionality and services offered on or through mywifequitherjob.com (the “Website”), whether as a guest or a registered user.

When accessing the Website, the Company will learn certain information about you, both automatically and through voluntary actions you may take, during your visit. This policy applies to information we collect on the Website and in email, text, or other electronic messages between you and the Website.

Please read the Privacy Policy carefully before you start to use the Website. By using the Website or by clicking to accept or agree to the Terms of Use when this option is made available to you, you accept and agree to be bound and abide by the Privacy Policy. If you do not want to agree to the Privacy Policy, you must not access or use the Website.

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU**  
When you access the Website, the Company will learn certain information about you during your visit.

The Website provides various places for users to provide information. We collect information that users provide by filling out forms on the Website, communicating with us via contact forms, responding to surveys, search queries on our search feature, providing comments or other feedback, and providing information when ordering a product or service via the Website.

We use information you provide to us to deliver the requested product and/or service, to improve our overall performance, and to provide you with offers, promotions, and information.

**Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technology**  
As you navigate through our Website, we may use automatic data collection technologies including Google Analytics to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns. This will generally include information about your location, your traffic pattern through our website, and any communications between your computer and our Website. Among other things, we will collect data about the type of computer you use, your Internet connection, your IP address, your operating system, and your browser type.

The information we collect automatically is used for statistical data and will not include personal information. We use this data to improve our Website and our service offerings. To the extent that you voluntarily provide personal information to us, our systems will associate the automatically collected information with your personal information.

**USE OF COOKIES AND PIXELS**  
Similar to other commercial websites, our website utilizes a standard technology called “cookies” and server logs to collect information about how our site is used. Information gathered through cookies and server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our site, and the websites visited just before and just after our own, as well as your IP address.

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a website, that site’s computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a website to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.

The Company reserves the right to use technological equivalents of cookies, including social media pixels. These pixels allow social media sites to track visitors to outside websites so as to tailor advertising messages users see while visiting that social media website. The Company reserves the right to use these pixels in compliance with the policies of the various social media sites.​

**THIRD PARTY USE OF COOKIES**  
Some content or applications, including advertisements, on the Website are served by third-parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers, and application providers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our website. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content.

We do not control these third parties’ tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly.

**EMAIL INFORMATION**  
If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received online, mail, and telephone. This also applies when you register for our website, sign up through any of our forms using your email address or make a purchase on this site. For further information see the email policies below.

**EMAIL POLICIES**  
We are committed to keeping your e-mail address confidential. We do not sell, rent, or lease our subscription lists to third parties, and will not disclose your email address to any third parties except as allowed in the section titled Disclosure of Your Information.

We will maintain the information you send via e-mail in accordance with applicable federal law.

In compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act, all e-mails sent from our organization will clearly state who the e-mail is from and provide clear information on how to contact the sender. In addition, all e-mail messages will also contain concise information on how to remove yourself from our mailing list so that you receive no further e-mail communication from us.

Our emails provide users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners by reading the unsubscribe instructions located at the bottom of any e-mail they receive from us at anytime.

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials may opt-out of receiving these communications by clicking on the unsubscribe link in the e-mail.

**HOW AND WHY WE COLLECT INFORMATION**  
The Company collects your information in order to record and support your participation in the activities you select. If you register to download a book or resources, sign up for our newsletter, and/or purchase a product from us, we collect your information. We use this information to track your preferences and to keep you informed about the products and services you have selected to receive and any related products and/or services. As a visitor to this Website, you can engage in most activities without providing any personal information. It is only when you seek to download resources and/or register for services that you are required to provide information.

If you are outside the European Union and opt to receive any free resources, participate in any free training programs, register for a webinar, register for a live event, register for a seminar, or purchase any products sold by the Company on this Website, we will automatically enroll ​you to receive our free email newsletter. If you do not wish to receive this newsletter, you can unsubscribe anytime. We include an “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of every email we send. If you ever have trouble unsubscribing, you can send an email to support@mywifequitherjob.com requesting to unsubscribe from future emails.

If you are in the European Union and opt to receive any free resources, participate in any free training programs, register for a webinar, register for a live event, register for a seminar, or purchase any products sold by the Company on this Website, we will only enroll ​you to receive our free email newsletter if you affirmatively consent to it. If you do not wish to receive this newsletter, you can unsubscribe anytime. We include an “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of every email we send. If you ever have trouble unsubscribing, you can send an email to support@mywifequitherjob.com requesting to unsubscribe from future emails.

**HOW DO WE USE THE INFORMATION THAT YOU PROVIDE TO US?**  
We use personal information for purposes of presenting our Website and its contents to you, providing you with information, providing you with offers for products and services, providing you with information about your subscriptions and products, carrying out any contract between you and the Company, administering our business activities, providing customer service, and making available other items and services to our customers and prospective customers.

From time-to-time, we may use the information you provide to us to make you offers to purchase products and services provided by third parties in exchange for a commission to be paid to us by such third parties. Should you opt to take part in such promotions, the third parties will receive your information.

From time-to-time, we may use the information you provide to us to display advertisements to you that are tailored to your personal characteristics, interests, and activities.

**DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION**  
As a general rule, we do not sell, rent, lease or otherwise transfer any information collected whether automatically or through your voluntary action.

We may disclose your personal information to our subsidiaries, affiliates, and service providers for the purpose of providing our services to you.

We may disclose your personal information to a third party, including a lawyer or collection agency, when necessary to enforce our terms of service or any other agreement between you and the Company.

We may provide your information to any successor in interest in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of the Company’s asserts and/or business.

We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights or when compelled by a court or other governmental entity to do so.

**HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION AND SECURE INFORMATION TRANSMISSIONS?**  
We employ commercially reasonable methods to ensure the security of the information you provide to us and the information we collect automatically. This includes using standard security protocols and working only with reputable third-party vendors.  Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this reason, we request that you do not send private information to us by email. However, doing so is allowed, but at your own risk. Some of the information you may enter on our website may be transmitted securely via a secure medium known as Secure Sockets Layer, or SSL. Credit Card information and other sensitive information is never transmitted via email.

The Company may use software programs to create summary statistics, which are used for such purposes as assessing the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, what information is of most and least interest, determining technical design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas.

For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, the Company uses software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage.

**POLICY CHANGES**  
It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users’ personal information, we will notify you by email to the email address specified in your account and/or through a notice on the Website home page. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the bottom of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable email address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes.

**VISITORS’ GDPR RIGHTS**  
If you are within the European Union, you are entitled to certain information and have certain rights under the General Data Protection Regulation. Those rights include:

We will retain the any information you choose to provide to us until the earlier of: (a) you asking us to delete the information, (b) our decision to cease using our existing data providers, or (c) the Company decides that the value in retaining the data is outweighed by the costs of retaining it.

You have the right to request access to your data that the Company stores and the rights to either rectify or erase your personal data.

You have the right to seek restrictions on the processing of your data.

You have the right to object to the processing of your data and the right to the portability of your data.

To the extent that you provided consent to the Company’s processing of your personal data, you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time, without affecting the lawfulness of processing based upon consent that occurred prior to your withdrawal of consent.

You have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority that has jurisdiction over issues related to the General Data Protection Regulation.

We require only the information that is reasonably required to enter into a contract with you. We will not require you to provide consent for any unnecessary processing as a condition of entering into a contract with us.

**CHILDREN UNDER THE AGE OF 13**  
Our Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any information to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on this Website or on or through any of its features/register on the Website, make any purchases through the Website, use any of the interactive or public comment features of this Website or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, email address, or any screen name or user name you may use.

If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at support@mywifequitherjob.com.

**AFFILIATE LINKS**  
Please note that some of the links on the blog are affiliate links, and at no additional cost to you, I will earn a commission if you decide to make a purchase. Please understand that I have experience with all of the companies that I mention, and I recommend them because they are helpful and useful, not because of the small commissions I make if you decide to buy something. Please do not spend any money on these products unless you feel you need them or that they will help you achieve your goals.

**SMS/MMS MOBILE MESSAGING MARKETING PROGRAM**

We respect your privacy. We will only use information you provide through the Program to transmit your mobile messages and respond to you, if necessary. This includes, but is not limited to, sharing information with platform providers, phone companies, and other vendors who assist us in the delivery of mobile messages.

WE DO NOT SELL, RENT, LOAN, TRADE, LEASE, OR OTHERWISE TRANSFER FOR PROFIT ANY PHONE NUMBERS OR CUSTOMER INFORMATION COLLECTED THROUGH THE PROGRAM TO ANY THIRD PARTY. Nonetheless, We reserve the right at all times to disclose any information as necessary to satisfy any law, regulation or governmental request, to avoid liability, or to protect Our rights or property. When you complete forms online or otherwise provide Us information in connection with the Program, you agree to provide accurate, complete, and true information.

You agree not to use a false or misleading name or a name that you are not authorized to use. If, in Our sole discretion, We believe that any such information is untrue, inaccurate, or incomplete, or you have opted into the Program for an ulterior purpose, We may refuse you access to the Program and pursue any appropriate legal remedies.

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits Users of the Program that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of the information you provide through the Program to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us at the following address:

When you visit our website, log in, register or open an email, cookies, ad beacons, and similar technologies may be used by our online data partners or vendors to associate these activities with information they or others have about you, including your email address. We (or service providers on our behalf) may then send communications and marketing to these email addresses. You may opt out of receiving this advertising by visiting https://app.getemails.com/optout.

### Mediavine Programmatic Advertising (Ver 1.1)

The Website works with Mediavine to manage third-party interest-based advertising appearing on the Website. Mediavine serves content and advertisements when you visit the Website, which may use first and third-party cookies. A cookie is a small text file which is sent to your computer or mobile device (referred to in this policy as a “device”) by the web server so that a website can remember some information about your browsing activity on the Website.

First party cookies are created by the website that you are visiting. A third-party cookie is frequently used in behavioral advertising and analytics and is created by a domain other than the website you are visiting. Third-party cookies, tags, pixels, beacons and other similar technologies (collectively, “Tags”) may be placed on the Website to monitor interaction with advertising content and to target and optimize advertising. Each internet browser has functionality so that you can block both first and third-party cookies and clear your browser’s cache. The “help” feature of the menu bar on most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new cookies, how to receive notification of new cookies, how to disable existing cookies and how to clear your browser’s cache. For more information about cookies and how to disable them, you can consult the information at [All About Cookies](https://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/).

Without cookies you may not be able to take full advantage of the Website content and features. Please note that rejecting cookies does not mean that you will no longer see ads when you visit our Site. In the event you opt-out, you will still see non-personalized advertisements on the Website.

The Website collects the following data using a cookie when serving personalized ads:

* IP Address
* Operating System type
* Operating System version
* Device Type
* Language of the website
* Web browser type
* Email (in hashed form)

Mediavine Partners (companies listed below with whom Mediavine shares data) may also use this data to link to other end user information the partner has independently collected to deliver targeted advertisements. Mediavine Partners may also separately collect data about end users from other sources, such as advertising IDs or pixels, and link that data to data collected from Mediavine publishers in order to provide interest-based advertising across your online experience, including devices, browsers and apps. This data includes usage data, cookie information, device information, information about interactions between users and advertisements and websites, geolocation data, traffic data, and information about a visitor’s referral source to a particular website. Mediavine Partners may also create unique IDs to create audience segments, which are used to provide targeted advertising.

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices to opt-in or opt-out of this data collection, please visit [National Advertising Initiative opt out page](https://thenai.org/opt-out/). You may also visit [Digital Advertising Alliance website](http://optout.aboutads.info/#/) and [Network Advertising Initiative website](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#) to learn more information about interest-based advertising. You may download the AppChoices app at [Digital Advertising Alliance’s AppChoices app](https://youradchoices.com/appchoices) to opt out in connection with mobile apps, or use the platform controls on your mobile device to opt out.

For specific information about Mediavine Partners, the data each collects and their data collection and privacy policies, please visit [Mediavine Partners](https://www.mediavine.com/ad-partners/).

**CONTACT US**  
MWQHJ LLC welcomes your questions or comments regarding the Privacy Policy:

MWQHJ LLC  
1050 Kiely Blvd #3495  
Santa Clara, CA 95055

Email Address: support@mywifequitherjob.com

This Privacy Policy is strictly limited to the Program and has no effect on any other privacy policy(ies) that may govern the relationship between you and Us in other contexts.

### Create A Profitable Online Store!

A completely **FREE** mini course on how to develop a niche ecommerce website in 5 easy steps!  
  
Learn how to find products to sell and setup your online store.  

Related Content

* [559: The Brutal Truth About Playing It Safe And Why It’s Holding You Back With Chase Jarvis](https://mywifequitherjob.com/episode559/)
* [557: Why You’ll Never Get Anywhere In Business If You Don’t Stop THIS Habit!](https://mywifequitherjob.com/episode557/)
* [556: What’s Really Going On? A Behind the Scenes Look At How We’re Changing Our Business](https://mywifequitherjob.com/episode556/)
* [555: The Secret To Crushing Black Friday Without Slashing Prices](https://mywifequitherjob.com/episode555/)
* [BMW Is Prioritizing Profit Over Safety—Here’s What You Need to Know](https://mywifequitherjob.com/bmw-is-prioritizing-profit-over-safety-heres-what-you-need-to-know/)
* [554: Turn First-Time Buyers Into Lifelong Customers with These Strategies](https://mywifequitherjob.com/episode554/)
* [553: Amazon & TikTok Join Forces! How Google’s Legal Woes Could Change E-Commerce Forever](https://mywifequitherjob.com/episode553/)
* [552: The Hidden Cost of Selling on Amazon: New Fees And Policy Changes With Yoni Mazor](https://mywifequitherjob.com/episode552/)
* [Why People Dumber Than You Are Millionaires (And What You Must Do Now)](https://mywifequitherjob.com/how-to-be-a-millionaire/)
* [551: How To Go On Vacation Without Your Business Falling Apart (w/ Few Employees)](https://mywifequitherjob.com/episode551/)
* [550: Why Content Creators Are Quitting: Is It Still Worth It?](https://mywifequitherjob.com/episode550/)
* [549: Big Tech Is Squeezing Your Business Dry (And What To Do About It)](https://mywifequitherjob.com/episode549/)
* [548: Amazon Declares War On Temu And Screws All Amazon FBA Sellers](https://mywifequitherjob.com/episode548/)
* [Walmart Sells Out To China And Betrays US Sellers To Fight Temu](https://mywifequitherjob.com/walmart-vs-temu/)
* [547: The Formula For Running A Record-Breaking Sale With Email Marketing](https://mywifequitherjob.com/episode547/)
* [546: Google Pisses Off Sellers And The Latest Updates From TikTok](https://mywifequitherjob.com/episode546/)
* [545: Expert Advice on Building a Massive Online Following With Nathan Barry](https://mywifequitherjob.com/episode545/)
* [544: It’s Game Over For Etsy Sellers In The US. Here’s What’s Happening…](https://mywifequitherjob.com/episode544/)

Where Should I Begin?

[

Click Here To Take My FREE 6 Day Ecommerce Mini Course](#minicourse)[

Click Here To Take My FREE 6 Day Amazon FBA Mini Course](#amazoncourse)[

Click Here To Take My FREE 6 Day Blogging Mini Course](#blogcourse)

#### Get Social

[MyWifeQuitHerJob.com](https://mywifequitherjob.com/) Copyright 2024 All Rights Reserved.

Please Read Our [Privacy Policy](https://mywifequitherjob.com/privacy-policy/) And [Terms Of Service](https://mywifequitherjob.com/terms-of-service/)

Everything you need to know on how to build a profitable ecommerce store from scratch!

* Completely free
* Easy to follow tutorials
* No Fluff

Enter your primary email address below and receive my FREE **6 Day Mini-Course** and weekly tips on How To Create A Profitable Online Store

Create A Profitable Online Store In 6 Easy Steps

Everything you need to know on how to grow your ecommerce store to 7 or 8 figures!

* Completely free
* Easy to follow tutorials
* No Fluff

Enter your primary email address below and receive my FREE **6 Day Mini-Course** on Advanced Strategies To Grow Your Online Store

Advanced Strategies To Grow Your Online Store

Everything you need to know to start a profitable blog and build an audience

* Find a profitable niche
* Setup a Wordpress blog
* Generate traffic to your site

Enter your primary email address below and receive my FREE **6 Day Mini-Course** and weekly tips on How To Create A Profitable Blog

Learn How To Start A Profitable Blog

Everything you need to know to sell on Amazon FBA the right way!

* Completely free
* Easy to follow tutorials
* No Fluff

This course is delivered via **email**. Follow the directions below and receive my FREE **6 Day Mini-Course** on How To Sell On Amazon FBA

A Crash Course On How To Sell On Amazon FBA

Everything you need to know to launch a successful product on Amazon from complete scratch!

* Step by step video
* Quick start PDF guide
* Text me your questions!

This lesson is delivered via **SMS text message**. Follow the directions below and receive my FREE **Bonus Lesson** on How To Get Started On Amazon

Thanks For Signing Up! Would You Like A FREE Bonus Lesson?
